What do you feel like the president should be doing?
A lot more.
Student loans. I think those should be next.
That's just my personal opinion.
Are you guys students?
I'm about to be one.
Ooh, what kind of student?
Medical student.
Ooh!
Yeah, you definitely want them loans licks.
So them loans don't chase you like me running for president.
So if you become president, that's my request to you.
Okay, okay. I mean, if I ran, do you think you would vote for me?
It depends.
Ooh!
What does it depend on?
Like, you know, what are you fighting for?
What am I fighting for?
Oh, you're really asking the real question.
You know what I'm fighting for?
I'm actually fighting for the people.
Okay.
Because I feel like what's happened now is we don't have public servants.
Yeah.
We have politicians.
If you could make a new law, what would it be?
Oh my gosh.
I know, right?
That's a huge question.
We have to imagine this way.
Yeah.
Is it like you want reparations for black people?
Is it you want like police to not have qualified immunity?
Is it that you want dad sneakers to be banned?
It could be anything.
It would have something to do with health care.
Health care.
Universal health care.
I think housing for all.
Housing for all.
Okay.
I was so noble of you.
I was not.
That's where it was good.
Oh.
Mine is like much more selfish.
I really like movies and movie theaters.
So like free movie theaters would be cool to me.
It's like free libraries.
I don't know.
Free movie theater concept.
You are the sixth grade class president who's like,
FIFA party.